Office of Public Relations Records UA063
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Public Relations Records
1937 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Public Relations
University Relations Division
UA063
46.19 Linear Feet 37 boxes
21 Digital Object(s)
The Office of Public Relations Records include scrapbooks, clippings, audiovisual materials, press releases, and subject files pertaining to Tufts, its students, alumni, and faculty.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into five series: Public Relations scrapbooks; Subject files; News releases and press kits; Audiovisual materials; and Unprocessed accessions.
Custodial History
Clippings were collected by the Office of Public Relations between 1941 and 1973.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains scrapbooks created by the Office of Public Relations containing clippings from local and national newspapers about Tufts, its students, alumni, and faculty. The collection also includes audiovisual materials, press releases, and subject files. Tufts University's alumni, commencement, and the Lincoln Filene Center are three significant topics in this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
University Relations; Facilities; Alumni and Alumni Relations
- Public Relations scrapbooks, 1937 -- 1973; 1941 -- 1973; UA063.001; 0.0 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains scrapbooks maintained by the Office of Public Relations of clippings from non-Tufts publications pertaining to the faculty, staff, students, and alumni of Tufts.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1944 -- 1946; UA063.001.001.001 (Box 1)
    Medals conferred on 7 graduates before 1,000 at Tufts Alumni day; [Alumni association] Distinguished service citation to Wilson L. Fairbanks, T1887; [alumni] Three Pote boys in service [includes photos]; [Alumni] Four Russell brother have reunion on medford [includes photos] served in armed forces; Alpha Tau Omega hosts christmas party for needy [includes photo], pg. 7; Alpha Xi Delta president elected, Miss Lois Jackson [includes photo]
    Volume
    2
    Office of Public Relations
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1946 -- 1947; UA063.001.002.001 (Box 2)
    [Alumni day] Elections to council and service award given [includes photos]; Alpha Xi Delta supports drive for Dutch relief [includes photo]; [Alumnae] plan fashion show for benefit of Alumnae hall fund
    3
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1947 -- 1948; UA063.001.003.001 (Box 3)
    Alumni day
    4
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1948 -- 1949; UA063.001.004.001 (Box 4)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Room dedicated in memory of Lt. Robert Atlas; Alumni day news clippings [includes photos]
    5
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1949 -- 1950; UA063.001.005.001 (Box 5)
    6
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1950 -- 1951; UA063.001.006.001 (Box 6)
    Thomas H. Alyden [1955] Awarded competative scholarship [photo included]
    7
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1951 -- 1952; UA063.001.007.001 (Box 7)
    [Alumni] Tufts Alumni testify; [Alpha Sigma Phi] Christmas party for South end children; Alpha Tau Omega honors 50 year members; Alpha Tau Omega Members contribute to "clean up Job" at Somerville Infirmary
    8
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1952; UA063.001.008.001 (Box 8)
    [Alumni association] Second century fund; [Alumni council] New members [includes photo]; Alumni day
    9
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1952 -- 1953; UA063.001.009.001 (Box 9)
    [Alumnae Hall] Architects drawing, clippings from Boston Sunday Herald, Boston Sunday Globe; Alumni day
    10
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1953 -- 1954; UA063.001.010.001 (Box 10)
    Alumni day news clippings; [Alumni association] Alumni awards newsclipping; [Alumnae Hall] Ground breaking; [Alpha Xi Delta] Tea to honor Ian Crane, Dutch student at Boston Conservatory of Music [Photo and news clippings, Boston Sunday Herald; Boston Sunday Post 11/22/1953], pg 48
    11
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1954 -- 1955; UA063.001.011.001 (Box 11)
    12
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1955; UA063.001.012.001 (Box 12)
    [American chemical society] New England Association meeting at Tufts; Alumni day news clippings; [Alumnae Hall] laying of cornerstone, clippings from Medford Mercury, Winchester Star [includes photo]
    13
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1937 -- 1956; UA063.001.013.001 (Box 13)
    14
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1957; UA063.001.014.001 (Box 14)
    Alumni day news clippings
    15
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1958; UA063.001.015.001 (Box 15)
    Alumni day; [Alumni council] Far east forum [includes photos], Panel of foreign affairs experts at 25th anniversary; [Alumni council] Alumni awards [includes photos]; Robert Alukonis [A1958] awarded Goddard Rhetorical Prize, recieved honorable mention in greenwood prize
    16
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1962-01-01 -- 1962-02-18; UA063.001.016.001 (Box 16)
  - Public Relations scrapbook, 1951 -- 1953; UA063.001.018.001 (Box 18)
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, Dental School Clippings, 1973; UA063.001.019.001 (Box 19)
  - Public Relations Scrapbook, 1941 -- 1944; UA063.001.020.001 (Box 20)
    1
- Subject files, 1975 -- 2014; 1965 -- 1984; UA063.002; 13.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains subject files collected and maintained by the Office of Communications. Topics include Tufts University programs, buildings, and departments, student activities, events, and organizations. Files contain newspaper clippings, public press releases or announcements, internal publications and documentation, and photographs. These materials were received in a group with no clear indication of the original order; folders have been rearranged according to an alphabetical structure based on original folder titles, which appear subject based. Users should think broadly about departments and programs when searching for specific information as some folders may seem out of order, e.g. "Civil Engineering" not "Engineering, Civil."
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Admissions, UA063.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, UA063.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Studies Program, UA063.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Artists, UA063.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Assoc. Awards, UA063.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Awards, UA063.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Council, UA063.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Field Reps., UA063.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Alumni and Parents, Eliot-Pearson Alum. Assoc., UA063.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Relations Office, UA063.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Scholarships, UA063.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Arena Theater, UA063.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Armenian Club, UA063.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Art, UA063.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Arts Commisson, UA063.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Arts Complex, UA063.002.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Asian Fellows, UA063.002.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, UA063.002.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Ballou Hall, UA063.002.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Band, Jazz Band, Jazz Choir, UA063.002.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Barnum Fire News Clips, UA063.002.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Biology, UA063.002.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Black Earth, UA063.002.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - BM Railroad/Tufts Station, UA063.002.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Bookstore, UA063.002.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Bradford Hotel Purchase for Medical School, UA063.002.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - BSOT, UA063.002.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - BSOT, UA063.002.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds, UA063.002.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Cabot Center, UA063.002.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Campus Buildings- General, UA063.002.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Carmichael Hall, UA063.002.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Campus Center, UA063.002.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Career Guidance and Placement, UA063.002.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Leonard Carmichael Soc. Kids Day, UA063.002.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, UA063.002.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Chaplaincy, UA063.002.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Chemistry, UA063.002.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Chemistry- Dana Foundation, UA063.002.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Child Study, UA063.002.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Classes Via Satellite, UA063.002.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Classical Institute, UA063.002.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Classics, UA063.002.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Cohen Arts Center, UA063.002.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - College Within, UA063.002.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - College Within, UA063.002.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - College Within Press Clip, UA063.002.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - College Within 3, UA063.002.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Commencement 1975-1976, UA063.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Commencement 1976-77, 1976 -- 1977; UA063.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1976 -- 1977; UA063.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1977 -- 1978; UA063.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1977 -- 1978; UA063.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1979; UA063.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA063.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1981; UA063.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1981; UA063.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1982; UA063.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1982; UA063.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - 120th Commencement Press Packet, UA063.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - 120th Commencement Press Packet, UA063.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, Hometowns, 1983; UA063.002.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, Speeches, 1983; UA063.002.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, Newsclips, 1983; UA063.002.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1983; UA063.002.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1984; UA063.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Commencement, 1984; UA063.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1984; UA063.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Newsclips, 1984; UA063.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Awards, 1984; UA063.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Honorary Degrees, 1984; UA063.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Vet School Grads Speakers, 1984; UA063.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Commencement, 1985; UA063.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Community Health, UA063.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Community Opera, UA063.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations/Chinatown, UA063.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations- General, UA063.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations- Head Start, UA063.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations- Housing, UA063.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations/Medford, UA063.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations/Medford Mercury, UA063.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations/Medford OPI Signs, UA063.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations/Somerville, UA063.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Community Relations/Somerville, UA063.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Computers, UA063.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Concerts at Tufts, UA063.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Conference Bureau, UA063.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education, UA063.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Counseling, UA063.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Cousens Gym, UA063.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Cousens Gym Expansion, UA063.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Crane Chapel, UA063.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - CUES Report, UA063.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Cup and Saucer, UA063.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Dana Biology Lab, UA063.002.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Dance at Tufts, UA063.002.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Day Care Center, UA063.002.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Decision Making, UA063.002.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Dental School, UA063.002.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Fernald Dental School, UA063.002.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Dining Services, UA063.002.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - DNA Research Ordinance, UA063.002.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Drama, UA063.002.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Drama, UA063.002.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Drama- Magic Circle, UA063.002.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Eastmoore Acad. Nantucket Assn., UA063.002.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - Economics, UA063.002.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Education, UA063.002.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - Education- Aid/Private Ed., UA063.002.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - Center for Educational Excellence in Teaching, UA063.002.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - Education- Civic Clips, UA063.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Education- Comments on, UA063.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Education- Committee Policy, UA063.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Education- Festival of Arts, UA063.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Electrical System, UA063.002.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Eliot-Pearson Literary #2, UA063.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Eliot-Pearson Literary #1, UA063.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Eliot Pearson Newsclips, UA063.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Eliot Pearson School, UA063.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Energy Committee, UA063.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Engineering- AIAA, UA063.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Engineering- Chemical, UA063.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Engineering- Citicar, UA063.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Engineering- Citicar, UA063.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Civil Engineering, UA063.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Civil Engineering, UA063.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/Colloquia, UA063.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Engineering Design, UA063.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Electrical Engineering, UA063.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - College of Engineering/100th Anniversary, UA063.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/General, UA063.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/General, UA063.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/GE Apprentice Program, UA063.002.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/Graphics and Design, UA063.002.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/Human Factors, UA063.002.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Mechanical Engineering, UA063.002.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Engineering Newsletter, UA063.002.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/SCORE, UA063.002.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Engineering/Students' Projects, UA063.002.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - English, UA063.002.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Ensembles- Music, UA063.002.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Ex-College/Bulletins, UA063.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College/General, UA063.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College/General, UA063.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College/General, UA063.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College Meetings, Mins., UA063.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College/Politics, UA063.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College Releases, UA063.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Ex-College/Zionism, UA063.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Lincoln Filene/ Asbestos CNT, UA063.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, UA063.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center, UA063.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center/Civil Div., UA063.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center Clips, UA063.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center/Environmental Conference, UA063.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center/General, UA063.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center/Hazardous Waste, UA063.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center Int. Rel., UA063.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center Pamphlets, UA063.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center Releases, UA063.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center Reports, UA063.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Filene Center Youth, Tchr., UA063.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - FIne Arts, UA063.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Fires, UA063.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Alums in Washington DC, UA063.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Arabs Bombing, UA063.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Arabs Clips, UA063.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Arabs Energy Program, UA063.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Arabs Latin America Sem., UA063.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Arabs Murrow Center, UA063.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Arabs Murrow Dedication, UA063.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher Cities Project, UA063.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher- Conferences, UA063.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Fulbright- Fletcher, UA063.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher- General, UA063.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher- General, UA063.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher- General, UA063.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Latin America Teaching Fellowship, UA063.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - LATF Venezuela, UA063.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher- Murrow Center, UA063.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher, Speakers at, UA063.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Franklin Park, UA063.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - French Institute, UA063.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Geology, UA063.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - German and Russian, UA063.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Goddard Chapel, UA063.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Graduate School, UA063.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Graduate School-Theses, UA063.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Haskell Dorm, UA063.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Health Care Program, UA063.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Delta Health Center, UA063.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Health Science Education, UA063.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Health Sci. Ed. Building, UA063.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Health Services, UA063.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Hillside Dorm, UA063.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Hillside School Purchase, UA063.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - History, UA063.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - HMO- Tufts University, UA063.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Homecoming Weekend, UA063.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Honorary Degrees, UA063.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, UA063.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Intercultural Center, UA063.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - International Relations, UA063.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Internships, UA063.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Jackson College, UA063.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Jackson College, UA063.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Jackson Dist. Service Award, UA063.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - The James Miller Band, UA063.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Latin Way Dorm, UA063.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Lewis Hall Dorm, UA063.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Mathematics, UA063.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Medford Campus Renovations, UA063.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Media Study Group, UA063.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Medical School, UA063.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Michael Chem Lab, UA063.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Miller Hall, UA063.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Mugar, UA063.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Murrow Center, 3rd World, UA063.002.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Murrow Center, 3rd World, UA063.002.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Murrow Center, 3rd World, UA063.002.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Museum School, UA063.002.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Music, UA063.002.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Music Hall, UA063.002.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Music Department, UA063.002.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - N.E. Conservatory of Music, UA063.002.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - New Dorms, 1979, UA063.002.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - News Clips- Alumni and Parents, UA063.002.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - North Hall, UA063.002.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Nutrition Center, UA063.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - School of Nutrition, UA063.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Nutrition Center, UA063.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Nutrition Newsletter, UA063.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Diet and Nutrition Newsletter Quotes, UA063.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Frances Stern Nutrition Institute, UA063.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Nutrition Institute Releases, UA063.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Nutrition Institute Research, UA063.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Oceanic Institute, UA063.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Opera, UA063.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Packard Hall, UA063.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Paige Hall, UA063.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Parents Council, UA063.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Parents Weekend, UA063.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Participant, etc., UA063.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Peddoks Island Trust, UA063.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Pediatric Complex, UA063.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Pep Program, UA063.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Personal Enrichment Program, UA063.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Personnel, UA063.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Philosophy, UA063.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Physical Education-Men and Women, UA063.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Physics, UA063.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Physiology, UA063.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Placement Office, UA063.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Plans of Study, UA063.002.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Police Department, UA063.002.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Political Science, UA063.002.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - President's Ball, UA063.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - President's Day, UA063.002.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Privacy Act, UA063.002.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Residents Halls-Houses, UA063.002.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Roots and Growth, UA063.002.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - ROTC, UA063.002.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - ROTC-Navy, UA063.002.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Sculpture, Campus, UA063.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Sheraton Commander, UA063.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Somerville Accident, UA063.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Talloires, UA063.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Taxing of University Property, UA063.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Abroad-Africa, UA063.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Abroad-England, UA063.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Abroad-Germany, UA063.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Abroad-Italy, UA063.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Abroad-London, UA063.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Abroad-Mexico, UA063.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Tufts in London-Photos, UA063.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Tufts MH Catchment, UA063.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Night at Pops, UA063.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Summer Day Camp, UA063.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Summer Program, UA063.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Tufts in Washington, UA063.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Undergraduate Education, UA063.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Unified Sci. Study Program, UA063.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - University Consortium, UA063.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - University Steering Committee, UA063.002.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Urban Study, UA063.002.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Warner Cable, UA063.002.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Wessell Library, UA063.002.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Wessell Library Comm, UA063.002.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - West Hall Fire, UA063.002.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Winners, UA063.002.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Winter Study, UA063.002.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Women's Club, UA063.002.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Wren Hall, UA063.002.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Year Round Operation, UA063.002.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Commencement and White Coat ceremonies, 2000 -- 2008; UA063.002.021 (Box 21)
    20 years from date of creation.
    Press releases, media advisories, programs, and articles related to Commencement and White Coat ceremonies, 2000-2008.
  - Commencement and White Coat ceremonies; various subject files, 1999 -- 2014; UA063.002.022 (Box 22)
    Press releases, media advisories, programs, and articles related to Commencement and White Coat ceremonies, 2009-2014; subject files on various topics from antibiotic resistance to vitamin E, 1999-2001.
- News releases and press kits, 1995 -- 2014; UA063.003; 6.0 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged as received from the Office of Public Relations.
  - FSNSP and HNRCA Nutrition Notes and media hits, 2000 -- 2007; UA063.003.022 (Box 22)
    Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (FSNSP) and Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging (HNRCA) Nutrition Notes (press releases), 2000-2007, and media hits.
  - FSNSP and HNRCA Nutrition Notes and media hits, 2000 -- 2007; UA063.003.023 (Box 23)
  - FSNSP and HNRCA Policy Points and top PR media hits, 1997 -- 2007; UA063.003.024 (Box 24)
    Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy (FSNSP) and Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging (HNRCA) Policy Points (press releases), 2004-2007, and top PR media hits, 1997-2005.
  - Press releases and brochures, 1999 -- 2014; UA063.003.025 (Box 25)
    Press releases; PR strategies; materials related to the 2007 School of Dental Medicine expansion; and brochures related to Health Sciences degrees, programs, and facilities.
  - Press releases and press kits, 1995 -- 2010; UA063.003.026 (Box 26)